ACTWU's Murray Finley Records from the President's Office 5619/036
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Crafted with Pride 1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Crafted with Pride 1986 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Crafted with Pride 1984 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- District Council # 37, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- "F" General, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- "G" General, 1984-1986 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- ACTWU - GEB - general, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- "H" General, 1982-1987 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- I General, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers Union - ILGWU, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- "J" Misc., 1985 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- California JT. BD.-cox-Rothster, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- California JT. BD., 1983 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- El Paso JT. BD 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Hudson Valley JT. BD. 1982-1983, 1982-1984 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Maine Joint Board, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Lehigh Valley JT. BD. 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Mid- Atlantic Region, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Midwest Regional Office - Textile, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Minnesota JT. BD., 1983 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Montreal JT. BD., 1983 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- New England Reg. JT. BD., 1982-1984 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- New York JT. BD., 1984 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- New York Neckwear Workers JT. BD., 1972-1983 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- North Jersey JT. BD. (Textile Division), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Pennsylvania JT. BD., 1984 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  One photograph
- Philadelphia Textile JT. BD., 1983 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Pittsburgh District JT. BD., 1985 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Rochester JT. BD., 1982-1984 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Rocky Mountain Dist. JT.BD., 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Schuylkill Valley & Garden Spot Joint Boards, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Shirt and leisurewear JT. BD., 19811983 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Southern New England JT. BD., 1983 (Box 51, Folder 32)
- Southern Regional JT. BD., 1982-1986 (Box 51, Folder 33)
- South Textile region JT. BD., 1982-1984 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- South Jersey JT. BD., 1983 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- South Regional JT. BD., 1982 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Textile Division - so. New England JT. BD., 1982-1983 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- "K" General, 1983-1985 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- "L" General, 1983-1985 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Labor Management Group, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Legal Department, 1981-1984 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Local 340, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- "N" General, 1984-1985 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- National Advisory Council on Economic Opportunity, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- National Assn. for the Advancement of colored people- NAACP, 1983-1986 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- "P" General, 1984-1985 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- "R" General, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- "S" General, 1983-1986 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- SUNY (Finley), 1985 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- "T" General, 1983-1985 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Target, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Target Sportswear Jesse Bayer, 1975-1984 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Textile division_-Engineering Dept., 1976-1983 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Union Prescription Centers, 1974-1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Union Label - Shirts, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Union Label Staff 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Unions Misc., 1984-1986 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Teamster, Chauffeurs, Ware-Houseman & Helpers of America, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- International confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1985 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- International federation of Chemical, Energy & General Workers Union - ICEF, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- International Federation of Chemical, Energy & General Workers Union - ICEF, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- International Longshoreman's Association, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- National Maritime Union, 1982-1984 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- National Union of Hospital & Health Care Employees (1199) (RWDSU-parent), 1986 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Seafarers international Union, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Teamsters, 1977-1985 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- United Electrical, Radio and Machine workers of America, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- United Farm workers of America AFL-CIO, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- United Federation of Teachers, 1975-1982 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- United hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- United Textile Workers, 1975-1982 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- "W" General, 1983-1985 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Work in American Institute, 1978-1982 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Xerox Agenda, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Xerox corp., 1974-1983 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Buy Xerox, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Xerox Special, 1983-1986 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous - 87, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous - 85-86, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Cotton Garment fund Cotfund 1986 Trustees Book (Box 54, Folder 2)
  Index cards
- Cotton Garment Fund 'I Comm' folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Board of Trustees Meeting' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Exec. Comm.' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'inv. Comm.' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Board of Trustees' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Sp. Inv. Comm.' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Board of trustees' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'I com - Apr. Report' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Mtg. Bd of T' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Cotton garment Fund 'Mtg. IC' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Cotton Garment Fund P.R Sub-Fund '85 Experience' Folder, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Bd T Q Invst. Reports' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'IC Cotfund' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'IC March Reports', 1986 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Sp Mtg.' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Cotton Garment Fund ' I reports Feb/ '86' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Cotton Garments Fund 'I Reports Jan. 86', 1986 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Cotton Garments Fund 'Minutes spec. Mtg. Cotfund' folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'EC Mtg Southern CA Sub-Fund' folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'Cotfund T Q Investment Report' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Cotton Garment Fund 'I C cotfund - Dec. Reports' Folders, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Cotton Garment fund - I C I Reports Nov. 85' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Alico Board of Directors' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Ex. Comm. Clofund' folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'ALICO I Comm' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Alico clothing Fund 'CLOFUND - I Comm.' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'I Comm.' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Bd. Of Dir. Mtg., 1986 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Board. Of Trustees Mtg.' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 29)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Board. Of Trustees Mtg.' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 30)
- Alico Clothing Fund - Board. Of trustees Mtg. 1st Half' Folder, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Alico clothing Fund 'I Com Alico' folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Board Dir Alico' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'S Mtg. Alico' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'NC Alico' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Q Investment reports', 1986 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'BD. Dir. By-Law Amendment' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Board. Dir.' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'IC AKUCT' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'IC ALICO' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'QA' folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Q Report Alico' folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'I com' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'EC' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'IC Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Alico Clothing Fund I Com. Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Alico Clothing Fund 'Q Investment Report' Folder, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Clofund 'Mo. Investment' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Clofund 'Q Summaries thru 9/30/84' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Clofund 'Q Investment rep.' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Clofund 'Mo. Investment' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Clofund 'Monthly Investment' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Clofund Monthly Investment reports Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Clofund Meeting Board trustees Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Clofund 'Cotfund' folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Clofund 'Mtg. Board. Of trustees' folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Clofund Meeting Exec.com Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Clofund 'Q Summaries' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Clofund 'Mtg investments com.' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Clofund Mo. Investment Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Clofund 'Q Report Board of Dir.' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 30)
- Clofund Monthly Investment Reports Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 31)
- Clofund 'Clofund Meetings' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 32)
- Clofund 'Clofund' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 33)
- Clofund 'Alico Investment com.' folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 34)
- Clofund 'Alico mo. Investment report' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 35)
- Clofund 'Alico Meetings' Folder, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 36)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Trustee/Advisory Exhibits (CLF. T/AC), 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Trustees Minutes", 1983 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Executive Committee Exhibits (CLF.EC), 1983 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Executive Comm. Minutes" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Executive Comm. Minutes" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Investment Committee Minutes" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Monthly Reports" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Quarterly Summaries" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Actuarial/Audit Reports" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Withdrawal Liability" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Book "Retirement Part (Pension Plan)" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustee Books "Insurance Part (Health & Welfare Plan)" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Insurance, Trustees Book Investment Transactions, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Alga mated Insurance, Trustee Book "Alico Exhibits (Alico)" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Alga mated Insurance, Trustee Book "Alico Minutes" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- (Clofund) "Executive Committee Exhibits (CLF. EC.)" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- (Clofund) "Executive Committee Minutes" Folder, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- (Clofund) "Monthly Reports" Folder, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- (Clofund) "Actuarial/Audit Reports" Folder, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- (Clofund) "Exhibits (Alico.)" Folder, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Alico Trustee Book "Clofund Meetings" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Alico Trustee Book "Clofund" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Alico Trustee Book "Alico Meetings" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Alico Trustee Book "Alico" Folder, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "PR Sub-Fund -13/31 1st 9 mo.exper.85" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Cotton garment Fund Trustees Book "12/10/86" Folder, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "12/9/85 - IC" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustee Book "Cotfund Q Invest. 11/18/85" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "Cotton/Board Trustee Mtg. 11/12/85" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "Cotfund - IC mtg 11/12/85, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "Cotfund/Trustees Q - Investment 11/1/85, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "cotfund - IC 11/1/85, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "Cotfund - 9/23/85 1/2 '85 PR Sub-F" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "6/4/85 Exec. Com" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "6/4/85 Invest. Com." Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Cotton Garment Fund trustees Book "5/29/85 Cotfund 1stQ Experience Retirement & Insurance Parts, PR Sub-Fund" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "Cotfund 4/3/85Mo. Investment Rep." Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Cotton Garment Fund Trustees Book "Cotfund -3/11/85 Q investments Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Clofund EC Mtg. 6/18/85, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Clothing Fund Alico "6/18/85 Clofund Invest. Comm" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Clothing Fund Alico "6/12/85 I C" folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Clofund - Q Inv 5/22/85" folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Clothing Fund Alico 6/12/85 - 1st Q Clofund, Southern CA retail retirement Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Clofund 3/11/85 Q investments" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico-12/10/85 Mo. Invest reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico -12/10/85 Mo. Invest Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Investment Co. 11/1/85 Alico" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico 11/18/85 Q Invest. Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico 10/16/85 Mo. Invest Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Clothing fund Alico "Alico 9/20/85 Mo. Invest reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico -9/6/85 Q. Invest Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 27)
- Clothing fund Alico "Alico 6/27/85 Mtg. Board. Of Dir." Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico 12/16/85 IC Mtg." folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico 8/14/85 Mo. Investment Report" folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 30)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico - 7/19/85 Mo. Investment Reports" Folder (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico S Mtg. 6/27/85" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 32)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico NC mtg. 6/27/85" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 33)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico 6/18/85 IC Mtg." folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 34)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico - 6/12/85 monthly Invest. Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 35)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico - 5/22/85 Q Invest. Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 36)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico - 4/19/85 Mo. Invest. Report." Folder (Box 58, Folder 37)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico - 4/3/85 Mo. Invest. Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 38)
- Clothing Fund Alico "Alico - 3/27/85 MO. Invest. Reports" Folder, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 39)
- Clofund 1985 "Clofund 11/1/85 Inv. Com" Folder (Box 58, Folder 40)
- Clofund 1985 "Clofund/Trustees So CA Retail Sub-Fund 9/23/85 (Box 58, Folder 41)
- Clofund 1985 "Clofund -12/16/85 IC Mtg." Folder (Box 58, Folder 42)
- Clofund 1985 "Clofund - 12/16/85 EC Mtg." folder (Box 58, Folder 43)
- Clofund 1985 "Clofund - 12/16/85 EAC Mtg." Folder (Box 58, Folder 44)
- Clofund 1985 "Clofund - 12/16/85 EC Mtg. (Box 58, Folder 45)
- Clofund1985 "Clofund T Mtg. 12/16/85" Folder (Box 58, Folder 46)
- Clofund 1985 "12/2/85 - I Com Review of Contracts" Folder (Box 58, Folder 47)
- Clofund 1985 "Clofund/Trustees Q Invest. 11/18/85 (Box 58, Folder 48)
- Clofund "Executive Committee Exhibits (CLF. EC.)" Folder, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Clofund "Trustees/Advisory Exhibits (CLF. T/AC)" Folder, 1979-1982 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Clofund "Alico Exhibits (Alico.)" Folder, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Clofund "Finance Committee Exhibits (CLF.FC.)" Folder, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Clofund 1982 "Executive Committee Exhibits (CLF.EC.)" Folder (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Clofund 1982 "Executive Committee Minutes" Folder (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Clofund 1982 "Trustees/Advisory Exhibits (CLF.T/AC)" Folder (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Clofund 1982 "Trustees/Advisory Minutes" Folder (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Clofund 1982 "Alico Exhibits (Alico)" Folder (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Clofund 1982 "Alico Minutes" Folder (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Clofund 1982 "Finance Comm. Exhibits" Folder (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Clofund 1982 "Executive Committee Exhibits (CT.EC.) (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Clofund 1982 "Executive Committee Minutes (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Clofund 1982 "Trustees Exhibits (CTF.T)" Folder (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Clofund 1982 "Financial Comm. Exhibits" folder (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Clofund 1982 "Actuarial/Adult Reports" Folder (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Clofund Book 2 "Monthly Reports" Folder, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Clofund 1982 "Executive Committee Minutes" Folder (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Clofund 1982 "Trustees/Advisory Minutes" Folder (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Clofund 1982 "Actuarial/Audit Reports" Folder, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Clofund Book 2 "Monthly Reports" folder, 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Clofund Book 2 "Executive Committee Minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Clofund Book 2 "Trustees/Advisory Minutes" Folder, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Clofund Book 2 "Alico Minutes" Folder, 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Clofund Book 2 "Actuarial/Audit Reports" Folder, 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Clofund Trustee Book "Cotfund Meetings" Folder, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Clofund Trustees Book "Cotfund" Folder, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- ACTWU comm. on organizing "Correspondence" Folder, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- ACTWU comm. on organizing "Analysis of Graphs" Folder, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- ACTWU comm. On organizing "Elections & RWE's" Folder, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- ACTWU comm. On organizing "Committee Studies" Folder, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- ACTWU comm. On organizing "Strategy for 1st Contract" folder, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Clofund book 1 "Executive Committee Exhibits" (CTF.EC.) Folder, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Clofund Book 1 "Trustees Exhibits (CTF.T.)" Folder, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Clofund Book 1 "Finance Committee Exhibits (CTF.FC.)" Folder, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Clofund Trustee Book 1 "Executive Comm. Minutes" Folder, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Clofund Trustees Book 1 "Trustees Exhibits (CTF.T.)" folder, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Clofund Trustees book 1 "Trustees minutes" Folder, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Clofund Trustees Book 1 "Monthly Reports" Folder, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Clofund Trustees Book 1 "Quarterly Summaries" folder, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Cotfund Trustees Book1 "Withdrawal Liability" Folder, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 16)